games-utilities.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Games UtilitiesGames Utilities

At Games-Utilities.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extremely importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Games-Utilities.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, http://www.Games-Utilities.com/ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**  
Games-Utilities.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

> **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
>  .:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
>  .:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
>  .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include.

Google Adsense, InfoLinks, CpmStar, Adbrite etc. You can check for the respective privacy policies on their websites.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Games-Utilities.com/ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Games-Utilities.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Games-Utilities.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Traffic Reports**

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded.

**Email Address**

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list or Feed Subscription via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

**Legal proceedings**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but Games-Utilities.com may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**

If Games-Utilities.com is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Email Address**

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

**Links**

Games-Utilities.com websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Games-Utilities.com

**Notification of Changes**

When Games-Utilities.com makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Comments/Message Boards**

Games-Utilities.com contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions regarding Games-Utilities privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.games-utilities.com/contact-us "Contact Games-Utilities").
